# Jonathan Moshier

CONTACT Information location: denver, co, usa telephone: 1 (303) 859-2569 email: jonmoshier@gmail.com

website: jonmoshier.com linkedin: linkedin.com/in/jmoshier github: github.com/jonmoshier

**OBJECTIVE** 

To work with smart, dedicated people, solving challenging problems and building great things. I'm at home on a fast moving team using agile processes with quick iterations. I love building robust usuable systems that make lives better.

Programming Skills Generalist, self taught, full stack developer. Full time Linux user, very comfortable with Linux server administration. I use AWS for deployment infrastructure and have built and managed continuous integration platforms for simplified DevOps. I'm very proficient with frontend technologies like HTML, CSS and Javascript/Typescript; as well as expert in backend technologies like Python, Django, Linux, C# and SQL.

Professional Experience -Software

# Transmed Systems, Washington, D.C.

Software Engineer

August 2010 – present

Was brought on as the 6<sup>th</sup> employee of this now 22 employee private company. I came on as a junior .net engineer, working with everything from company infrastructure to user facing products. Our primary product is a browser based BioInformatics platform, that allows clinicians to analyze hospital data.

- Lead architect, developer & project owner for our applications data importer. Allows users to import Excel spreadsheets into our applications database for analysis. This tool uses Silverlight, C#, and MS SQL.
- Lead architect, developer & project owner of an audit logging and reporting system using log4net, ASP.net, C#, and logparser, an existing tool that allows flat files to be queried using SQL statements.
- System Administration using CentOS to develop an analytics package using R/Rserve, tested the analysis tools package using Amazon's AWS as well as in-house servers before deploying to customer sites.

Worked on various "nuts-and-bolts" jobs, including:

- Switching our company wide email to Google apps.
- Building our continuous deployment process using TFS and MSBuild.
- Stress testing our application using 3<sup>rd</sup> party tools.

Professional Experience -Non-Software

## The Kitchen Cafe, Boulder, Colorado, USA

Line Chef

February 2009 – July 2010

- Worked all stations in this two kitchen, two dining room restaurant
- Ran the [Upstairs] kitchen and menu two nights a week providing excellent casual food for a Lounge/Bar restaurant setting

#### FreeWave Technologies, Boulder, Colorado, USA

Customer Support Technician and Inside Sales Representative April 2006 – December 2006

- Worked with customers via phone, email and in person to help understand radio application and configuration
- Lead Export Management Group to ensure compliance with all U.S. Export Laws

EDUCATION

### University of California Santa Cruz Extension, Santa Clara, California, USA

Extracurricular learning in

September 2010 - March 2011

- C# Programming for the .Net Framework
- Molecular Biology

#### University of Colorado Boulder, Boulder, Colorado, USA

Bachelors of Science, Economics

August 2009